Guide to the Montana State University Extension Service Records 1912-1970
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- County and Home Demonstration Agents Annual Reports, 1916-1970; 1
  - Flathead County; Lillian Tubb, H.D.A., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Flathead County; Leonard Eliason, C.A., 1943 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Flathead County; Helen M. Everson, H.D.A., 1943 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Flathead County; Leonard Eliason, C.A., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Flathead County; Helen Everson, H.D.A., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Flathead County; Leonard Eliason, W. W. Mauritson, C.A.s, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Flathead County; Helen Everson, H.D.A., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, C.A., 1946 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Flathead County; Helen Ellison, Lucile Nelson, H.D.A.s, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, C.A., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Flathead County; Helen Everson, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Flathead County; Helen Everson Prince, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Flathead County; Lillian Tubb, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Flathead County; Lillian Tubb, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, Lillian Tubb, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 17-18)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, Lillian Tubb, James Yocum, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, Marvin Costello, Lillian Tubb, Fay McNabb, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, Lillian Tubb, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, Lillian Tubb, Fay M. White, Marvin Costello, Julie Case, Avis Griffith, Robert Ruthemeyer, Orville W. McCarver, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Flathead County; Mauritson, Tubb, Costello, Case, McCarver, Ruthemeyer, Wheeler, Wearne, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, Lillian Tubb, Julie Case, Marvin Costello, Bill Richter, R. A. Olson, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, Agent; Lillian Tubb, H.D.A.; Marvin Costello, Assoc.; Audrey Davies, Assoc., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, Lillian Tubb, Audrey Davies, W. Doyle Stocks, Marvin Costello, Art Lyman, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Flathead County; W. W. Mauritson, Allen Nelson, Doyle Stocks, Lillian Tubb, Audrey Davies, Allene Willson, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Flathead County; Allen Nelson, W. Doyle Stocks, Louis Rollman, Allen M. Willson, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Flathead County; Allen Nelson, Doyle Stocks, Noble Dean, Allene Willson, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Flathead County; Allen Nelson, Nobel Dean, Allene Pierce, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Flathead County; Allen Nelson, Allene Pierce, Noble Dean, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Flathead County; Merle Lyda, Allen Nelson, Allene Pierce, Richard Lovec, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Flathead County, 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 33-36)
  - Gallatin County; Geo. H. Cook, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Gallatin County; R. E. Bodley, C.A., 1920-1933 (Box 24, Folder 2-15)
  - Gallatin County; R. E. Bodley, George Woolley, C.A.s, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Gallatin County; George A. Woolly, C.A., 1935-1943 (Box 24, Folder 17-25)
  - Gallatin County; G. A. Woolly, Joe R. Anderson, C.A.s, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Gallatin County; George A. Wolley, C.A., 1945-1947 (Box 24, Folder 27-29)
  - Gallatin County; Arthur Shaw, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Gallatin County; Gale Ueland, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Gallatin County; Arthur Shaw, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Gallatin County; Clare G. Morris, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Gallatin County; Arthur Shaw, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Gallatin County; Clare G. Morris, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Gallatin County; Owen S. Wirak, Clare Morris, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin County; Owen S. Wirak, Clare G. Morris, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin County; Owen Wirak, Clare Morris, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Gallatin County; Owen S. Wirak, Lucille Nelson, Marjorie Hacking, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Gallatin County; Marjorie Hacking, Owen Wirak, Jack Stover, John Calhoun, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Gallatin County; Marjorie Hacking, Vanetta Lewis, Douglas Smith, Jack Stover, Owen Wirak, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Gallatin County; Owen Wirak, C. Eugene Phillips, Venetta Lewis, Mabel Klosterboer, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Gallatin County; Mabel Klosterboer, H.D.A.; Owen Wirak, C.A.; Eugene Phillips, C.A. At Large, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Gallatin County; Mabel Klosterboer, Owen Wirak, Tom Glennie, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Gallatin County; Mabel Klosterboer, Owen S. Wirak, Mary S. Brown, Thomas N. Glennie, Burton Nagle, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Gallatin County; Dana Schrupp, Beulah McNeal, Vic Hoxsey, Mary Brown, Owen Wirak, Burton Nagle, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Gallatin County; Dana Schrupp, Anthony Sundsted, Beulah McNeal, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Gallatin County; Dana Schrupp, Beulah McNeal, William Gibson, Larry Marrow, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Gallatin County; Dana Schrupp, William Gibson, Beulah McNeal, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Gallatin County; Dana Schrupp, Beulah McNeal, Bill Gibson, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Gallatin County, 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 20-24)
  - Emergency Report, Garfield and Petroleum Counties; Thos. Hunt, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Garfield and Petroleum Counties; Stanley N. Halvorson, A.A., 1935 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Garfield and Petroleum Counties; O. A. Lammers, 1936-1938 (Box 26, Folder 3-5)
  - Garfield and Petroleum Counties; O. A. Lammers, M. H. Zimmerman, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Garfield and Petroleum Counties; M. H. Zimmerman, C.A., 1940 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Garfield and Petroleum Counties; Maurice H. Zimmerman, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Garfield County; M. H. Zimmerman, 1942-1943 (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
  - Garfield County; John Coston, C.A., 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 11-12)
  - Garfield County; John Coston, William Richter, C.A.s, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Garfield County; William R. Richter, 1960-1961 (Box 26, Folder 14-15)
  - Garfield County; William R. Richter, Lester Guptill, Jr., 1962 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Garfield County; Lester Guptill, Jr., 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 17-18)
  - Garfield County; Lester R. Guptill, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Garfield County; Lester Guptill, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Garfield County, 1967-1970 (Box 26, Folder 21-24)
  - Glacier and Toole Counties; A.L. White, C.A., 1928 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Glacier and Toole Counties; A. L. White, C.A., 1929 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Glacier County; A. L. White, C.A., 1930-1936 (Box 26, Folder 27-33)
  - Glacier County; A. L. White, R. G. Newell, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Glacier County; Robert. G. Newell, C.A., 1938-1945 (Box 26, Folder 35-42)
  - Glacier County; L. E. Flesch, C.A., 1946 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Glacier County; L. E. Flesch, C.A., 1947 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Glacier County; Cut Bank- Louise S. Shunk, H.D.A. at Large, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Glacier County; Larry Flesch, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Glacier County; Mrs. Louise Shunk, H.D.A. at Large, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Glacier County; Larry Flesch, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Glacier County; R. A. Roush, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Glacier County; R. A. Roush, Alice Finely, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Glacier County; Robert A. Roush, Bonita Olney, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Glacier County; Robert Roush, Bonita Olney, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Glacier County; John O. Toliver, Bonita Olney, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Glacier County; John O. Toliver, Robert E. Durham, Bonita J. Olney, 1955-1957 (Box 27, Folder 11-13)
  - Glacier County; John Toliver, Agent; Bonita Olney, H.D.A.; Robert Durham, A.A., 1958 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Glacier County; John O. Toliver, Agent; Robert Durham, Associate, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Glacier County; John O. Toliver, Robert E. Durham, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Glacier County; Joseph Rose, John Toliver, Robert Durham, Dorothy Gallup, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Glacier County; Joseph C. Rose, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Glacier County; Joseph C. Rose, Charles E. Egan, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Glacier County; Charles E. Egan, 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 20-22)
  - Glacier County, 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 23-26)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties; F. B. Peterson, C.A., 1934-1946 (Box 27, Folder 27-39)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties; B. W. Brink, C.A., 1947-1949 (Box 27, Folder 40-42)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties; James K. Ross, 1950-1954 (Box 27, Folder 43-47)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties; James K. Ross, C.A., 1955-1959 (Box 28, Folder 1-5)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties; James K. Ross, C. Eugene Phillips, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties; C. Eugene Phillips, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties; C. Eugene Phillips, Alvin Kilmer, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties; Alvin Kilmer, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties; Alvin Kilmer, Darryld Kautzman, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties; Darryld Kautzman, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties; Darryld Kautzman, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Golden Valley and Musselshell Counties, 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 13-16)
  - Granite County; W. D. Ross, Emergency Agent, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Granite County; J. H. Mikkelson, C.A., 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 18-19)
  - Granite County; H. Dawes, Lott, C.A., 1947 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Granite County; Dawes Lott, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Granite County; Richard Hedges, 1949-1950 (Box 28, Folder 22-23)
  - Granite County; Howard L. Tegland, 1951-1953 (Box 28, Folder 24-25)
  - Granite County; Submitted by 4-H, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Granite County, 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 28-31)
  - Hill County; Paul P. Banker, 1915-1919 (Box 28, Folder 32-36)
  - Hill County; Louis A. Campbell, 1920-1921 (Box 28, Folder 37-38)
  - Hill County; E. B. Duncan, C.A., 1924-1927 (Box 28, Folder 39-42)
  - Hill County; B. H. Daggett, C.A., 1928 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Hill County; Ben H. Daggett, C.A., 1929 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Hill County; E. H. Sandberg, C.A., 1930-1933 (Box 28, Folder 45-48)
  - Hill County; E. H. Sandberg, Ben Daggett, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Hill County; Ben H. Daggett, C.A., 1935-1936 (Box 28, Folder 50-51)
  - Hill County; B. H. Daggett, 1937-1942 (Box 29, Folder 1-6)
  - Hill County; Wietske Bydeley, H.D.A., 1942 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Hill County; Ben H. Daggett, C.A., 1943 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Hill County; Wietske Bydeley, H.D.A., 1943 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Hill County; Ben H. Daggett, C.A., 1944 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Hill County; Wietske Bydeley, H.D.A., 1944 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Hill County; Ben Daggett, C.A., 1945 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Hill County; Wietske Bydeley, H.D.A., 1945 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Hill County; R. F. Rasmussen, C.A., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Hill County; Havre- Wietske Bydeley, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Hill County; R. F. Rasmussen, C.A., 1947 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Hill County; Mary Grey, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Hill County; R. F. Rasmussen, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Hill County; Mary F. Grey, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Hill County; R. F. Rasmussen, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Hill County; Mary F. Grey, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Hill County; R. F. Rasmussen, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Hill County; Mary Grey, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Hill County; R. F. Rasmussen, Claire Vangelisti, 1951-1954 (Box 29, Folder 24-27)
  - Hill County; R. F. Rasmussen, R. F. Bucher, R. A. Roush, Edward H. Jabs, Claire Vangelisti; pages 1-108, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Hill County; R. F. Rasmussen, R. F. Bucher, R. A. Roush, Edward H. Jabs, Claire Vangelisti; pages 109-235, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Hill County; Robert F. Bucher, Robert A. Roush, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Hill County; R. F. Bucher, R. A. Roush, Ruth M. Poetter, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Hill County; Robert F. Bucher, Agent; Robert A. Roush, Assoc.; Ruth Mae Poetter, H.D.A., 1958 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Hill County; Bob Bucher, Richard Pulis, Bob Roush, Ruth Mae Poetter, Myrtle Bosch, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Hill County; Richard H. Pulis, Miriam O. Woosley, Robert A. Roush, Myrtle F. Bosch, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Hill County; Richard Pulis, Douglas Smith, Robert Roush, Miriam Woosley, Avis Stapleton, M. F. Bosch, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Hill County; Douglas G. Smith, Miriam O. Woosley, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Hill County; Doyle Stocks, Miriam Woosley, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Hill County; W. Doyle Stocks, Judith Gorden, Miriam Woosley, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Hill County; W. Doyle Stocks, Judith Gorden, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Hill County; Doyle Stocks, Russell Harris, Judith Gorden, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Hill County, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 9-12)
  - Jefferson County; Geo. W. Gustafson, 1921 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Charles Jarrett, Emergency Agent, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Noland A. Jacobsen, Emergency Agent, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Francis L. Niven, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; F. L. Niven, 1937-1939 (Box 30, Folder 17-19)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; F. L. Niven, Jack L. Maguire, Agents, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Jack L. Maguire, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Jack Maguire, Joe Leonard, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Joe Leonard, C.A., 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 23-25)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; H. A. Cosgriffe, C.A., 1946-1950 (Box 30, Folder 26-30)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Edwin D. Atkins, 1951-1954 (Box 30, Folder 31-34)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Edwin D. Atkins, Herbert Townsend, Elvin Powell, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Elvin A. Powell, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; E. A. Powell, W. Allen Turvey, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Elvin A. Powell, C.A., 1958-1960 (Box 31, Folder 2-4)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Elvin A. Powell, C. Arthur Lyman, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Arthur Lyman, Allen Bjergo, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Allen C. Bjergo, Karren P. Kembel, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties; Allen Bjergo, Roger Ogden, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties, 1967-1970 (Box 31, Folder 10-13)
  - Jefferson and Madison Counties, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Judith Basin County; C. R. Mountjoy, C.A., 1926-1928 (Box 31, Folder 14-16)
  - Judith Basin County, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Judith Basin County; C. R. Mountjoy, C.A., 1930 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Judith Basin County; C. R. Mountjoy, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Emergency Report, Judith Basin County; R. W. Sharples, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Judith Basin County; H. L. Dusenberry, Emergency Agent, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Judith Basin County; H. l. Dusenberry, C.A, 1935-1940 (Box 31, Folder 22-27)
  - Judith Basin County; Harold L. Dusenberry, Gerald O. Behimer, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Judith Basin County; G. O. Behimer, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Judith Basin County; Allen P. Nelson, C.A., 1946-1952 (Box 31, Folder 30-36)
  - Judith Basin County; Allen P. Nelson, C.A., 1953-1960 (Box 32, Folder 1-8)
  - Judith Basin County; Joseph C. Rose, Allen Nelson, Joseph W. Morris, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Judith Basin County; Joseph W. Morris, 1962-1966 (Box 32, Folder 10-14)
  - Judith Basin County, 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 15-18)
  - Lake County; L. B. Miller, C.A., 1925-1927 (Box 32, Folder 19-21)
  - Lake County; L. B. Miller, F. I. Peterson, C.A.s, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Lake County; G. A. Woolley, C.A., 1929-1933 (Box 32, Folder 23-27)
  - Lake County; G. A. Woolley, J. C. Paisley, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Lake County; J. C. Paisley, C.A., 1935 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Lake County; J. C. Paisley, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Lake County; J. C. Paisley, I. D. Zobell, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Lake County; I. D. Zobell, C.A., 1938-1941 (Box 32, Folder 32-35)
  - Lake County; I. D. Zobell, G. W. Johnson, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Lake County; Geo. W. Johnson, C.A., 1943 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Lake County; K. W. Fitzgerald, C.A., 1944 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Lake County; K. W. Fitzgerald, C.A., 1945 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Lake County; C. W. Roath, C.A., 1946-1947 (Box 33, Folder 2-3)
  - Lake County; C. W. Roath, Henry K. Botch, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Lake County; Henry K. Botch, Wm. P. Thomas, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Lake County; Henry K. Botch, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Lake County; H. K. Botch, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Lake County; Marion T. Hedegaard, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Lake County; Marion Hedegaard, Pat Flynn, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Lake County; Marion T. Hedegaard, Vernor Sande, Patricia Flynn, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Lake County; Marion Hedegaard, Raymond Stack, V. Sande, R. Bond, Patricia Flynn, Joan Monson, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Lake County; Raymond Stack, Thomas Woodbridge, Orville McCarver, Patricia Flynn, Joan Monson, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Lake County; Raymond Stack, Ed Bratton, Orville McCarver, Joan Helterline, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Lake County; Raymond Stack, Joan Helterline, Edward Bratton, Theodore Witzel, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Lake County; Ray Stack, Joan Helterline, Edward Bratton, Theodore Witzel, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Lake County; S. J. Tietema, Joan Helterline, Donald Gill, Wayne Gibson, Raymond Stack, Theo. Witzel, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Lake County; S. J. Tietema, Lillian Tubb, Donald Gill, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Lake County; S. J. Tietema, Ed Bratton, Lillian Tubb, Donald Gill, Wayne Gibson, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Lake County; Ed Bratton, Wayne Gibson, Lillian Tubb, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 19-20)
  - Lake County; G Edward Bratton, Lillian Tubb, Jane Campbell, Wayne Gibson, John Maki, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Lake County; Ed Bratton, John Maki, Jane Campbell, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Lake County, 1967-1970 (Box 33, Folder 23-26)
  - Lewis and Clark County; F. B. Carpenter, 1915 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Paul Carpenter, 1916 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Waldo W. Skuse, 1917-1918 (Box 33, Folder 29-30)
  - Lewis and Clark County; J. W. Manning, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Lucile Reynolds, Fay Wilcox, Mollie Feil, H.D.A.s, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Lewis and Clark County; J. W. Manning, 1920 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Inez B. Swan, H.D.A., 1920 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Lewis and Clark County; J. W. Manning, 1921 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Inez Swan, Bess I. Snyder, H.D.A.s, 1921 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Lewis and Clark County; J. W. Manning, W. H. Sutton, 1922 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Bess Snyder Sparrow, H.D.A., 1922 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Lewis and Clark County; W. H. Sutton, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Bess Snyder Sparrow, Nora L. Hulbush, H.D.A.s, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Lewis and Clark County; L. G. DeVore, 1924 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Nora L. Hulbush, H.D.A., 1924 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Lewis and Clark County; L. G. DeVore, C.A., 1925 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Nora L. Hulbush, H.D.A., 1925 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Lewis and Clark County; L. G. DeVore, C.A., 1926 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Nora Hulbush, H.D.A., 1926 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Lewis and Clark County; L. G. DeVore, C.A., 1927 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Nora Hulbush, H.D.A., 1927 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Lewis and Clark County; L. G. DeVore, C.A., 1928 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Nora Hulbush, Neva Woods, H.D.A.s, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Lewis and Clark County; R. E. Ward, C.A., 1929 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Neva Woods, H.D.A., 1929 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Lewis and Clark County; R. E. Ward, C.A., 1930 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Neva Woods, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Lewis and Clark County; R. E. Ward, C.A., 1931 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Neva E. Wood, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Lewis and Clark County; R. E. Ward, C.A., 1932 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Neva Woods Magraw, H.D.A., 1932 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Lewis and Clark County; R. E. Ward, C.A., 1933 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Neva Wood Magraw, H.D.A., 1933 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Lewis and Clark County; R. E. Ward, Mrs. Neva W. Magraw, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Mrs. Neva W. Magraw, H.D.A., 1934 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Lewis and Clark County; R. E. Ward, Waldo Zirnstein, C.A.s, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Neva Magraw, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Lewis and Clark County; W. O. Zirnstein, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Mrs. Neva W. Magraw, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Lewis and Clark County; W. O. Zirnstein, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Mrs. Neva Magraw, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Mrs. Neva W. Magraw, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1939-1941 (Box 34, Folder 26-28)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Florence Schuerman, H.D.A., 1942-1944 (Box 34, Folder 29-31)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Florence Schuerman, H.D.A., 1945 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Helena- Florence Schuerman, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Florence Schuerman, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Lewis and Clark County; C. W. Vaughn, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Florence Schuerman Reissing, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Clifford Vaughn, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Florence S. Reissing, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Lewis and Clark County; C. W. Vaughn, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Florence Reissing, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Lewis and Clark County; C. W. Vaughn, Florence Reissing, 1951-1954 (Box 35, Folder 10-13)
  - Lewis and Clark County; C. W. Vaughn, Patricia Sias, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Patricia Sias, C. W. Vaughn, James Sargent, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Lewis and Clark County; James F. Sargent, Patricia Sias, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Patricia Sias, H.D.A.; James Sargent, Agent; Catherine Walsh, Assoc. H.D.A., 1958 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Lewis and Clark County; Patricia Sias, H.D.A.; Catherine Walsh, Assoc. H.D.A.; James F. Sargent, Agent, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Lewis and Clark County; James Sargent, Catherine Walsh, Patricia Sias, Noble Dean, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Lewis and Clark County; James F. Sargent, Patricia Sias, Catherine Walsh, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Lewis and Clark County; James F. Sargent, Patricia S. Sias, Catherine Walsh, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Lewis and Clark County; James Sargent, Pat Sias, Roger Wilson, Frank Carter, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 22)